If you are a senior citizen and are looking for a good
health insurance then this
video is definitely for you and if your
parents are senior citizens then do not
forget to share this video with them.  We will discuss the
top five health insurance plans
for senior citizens.  Before starting the video, I would like to
introduce myself.
My name is Gurleen Coticu.  I am a
Certified Financial Planner.  I have been associated
with the insurance industry for the last 20 years
and bring new videos for you every week.
So that your
insurance buying journey and personal
finance journey becomes very good.
Because the tagline of our company is also
Creating a Wealth of Happiness.  Let's move on to the
video.  But before that, a quick
reminder, if you haven't subscribed to our channel yet, do so.
So that
you get the useful information at the right
time.  So today we will talk in detail about the five
best health insurance plans for
senior citizens.  So we have shortlisted five plans.  The
first is Neevapa Reash
2.2, the second is HDFCO Optima Secure.  Then we
have ICIC Elevate.  Fourth we have Aditya
Birla Active One Max Plan.  And fifth is we
have Manipal Cigna Saravah Param Plan.
So we will compare these five plans
on different parameters.  Let's see what are the
differences between them?  What are their benefits
?  This is the eligibility criteria for purchasing the policy.
Who can take this policy
?  And finally, we will talk about the
premiums and how much these policies actually
cost.  So stay till the end of the video.  This is going to be a
very useful video
for you.  Before talking about the
benefits and features.  First, let's talk about the
incurred claim ratio.
What is the Incurred Claim Ratio?  Are.  So,
as you know, the Incurred Claim Ratio is the amount
settlement ratio.  How many claims
came to the company, how much amount did they
settle?  That is called Inc. Claim Ratio.
So Niva Reader has an incurred claim ratio of 2.2,
HDFC Argo is 59.02%, ICICI Lo LBD
is 78.85, Aitya Birla is 68.31, Manipal
Sagnar is 63.78. Now let's talk about
what is special about these plans?  What is the USP
of these plans? Each one of them is individually the first one being
Neevapa Reshore 2.0. The USP of this
plan is that it has a feature called
Lock the Clock, which means your premium gets
locked at the current age until you make a claim.
Only the edge is locking.  Your
inflation is not locked in.  The age will be locked
until you make your first claim on the
policy.  The second benefit is that your
sum assured here goes up to 10 times.
Meaning, if you have taken a policy of Rs 10 lakh
and you are not using it, then in 10 years
it will become Rs 1 crore.  So every year 10
times gets added to the policy, which means whatever
unutilized sum assured you will not use will be
added and maximum it will go up
to 10 times.  Now let's talk about HDFC
Ergo Optima Secure.  Its USP is that
you get 2x 3x cover from day one.  HDFC Ergo Optima Secure offers two
to three times coverage.
Like you are paying a premium of Rs 10 lakh.
You have taken Optima Secure policy for one year.
It will be counted as 20 lax.  You have
taken a three years policy which is
Optima Super Secure.  So a policy of 10 lakhs
will be counted as 30 lakhs.  Secondly,
in this plan you get plus benefit
which is loyalty addition.  So what does the loyalty addition
say about whether you should claim the policy
or not?  Meaning it is not claim based.
It is just loyalty that you are continuing with the company.  The
company will give you 50%
additional sum assured in the second year and
50% in the third year.  So after 3 years your
policy increases by one X.
Next is ICICI LBA's Elevate plan.  So
here are some of the many add-ons that you
can consider as a USP.  So there are a lot of
add ons like Power Booster
where your sum assured increases every year.  There
is no maximum limit.  Cibil
discount is available.  If your credit
score is good then you are given a SIB discount.
And there are many more riders
which we will discuss in detail in the video further.
Then we come to Aditya Birla Active
One Max plan.  So there is
no maximum entry age limit in this plan.  This
is a USP.  Secondly, your sum assured goes up
to 5x.  You took a policy of Rs 10 lakh today.
Next year it will be 20, 30,
doing this will go up to five times.  This
is irrespective of the claim.  There
is no claim link inside it.  Last is the Manipal Cigna
Saravah Param Plan.  This plan
comes without any waiting period.  There
is no waiting period here.
You can take this plan with zero waiting period.
So, now let's talk about the eligibility
criteria.  First let us talk about minimum
and maximum entry age.  The
minimum entry age in Nibu Reshore 2.0 is 18 years, there is
no maximum limit.  You
can enter this policy at any age.
In HDFC Ergo Optima Secure also, the minimum
entry age for adults is 18 years and there is
no maximum limit.  The
minimum entry age at ICIC LBAD Elevate is 18 years.
The maximum is 125 years.  So you can understand that there is
no age limit.  The
minimum entry age for Aditya Birla Active & Max is also
18 years.  There
is no maximum limit.  In ManipalCigna Sarvaha
plan also the minimum entry age for an
adult is 18 years.  Maximum there is no
limit.  So now let's talk about room rent
eligibility.
What room rent is covered in your plan?  How
is it covered?  There are no limits in Neevapar Reshore 2.0.
Actuals claim will be given on age.  There is
no room rent limit in HDFC Urgo Optima Secure also.
Actuals will be given to you as per the claim.  Then comes
ICIC lobed elevate.  Here by
default single private AC room is covered.
If you want to get your room modified, you can
take the room modification rider.  And you
can upgrade and downgrade your room.  You
want to get treatment on twin sharing basis.
So you can take twin sharing.
You want to take the option of any room.
You do not have to keep any restriction that there should be no
room rent capping.  So
you can choose any room in the room modification writer.
Followed by Aditya Birla Active One
Max.  There is no capping for you in this also.
You can choose any room.  Then comes Manipal
Cigna Sarwaha Ultimate Plan.  Here you have a
single private AC room by default.   There is
no room rent capping on ICU.
Room modification rider is also available here.
You can add on if you do
n't want any room restrictions.  Now let us
come to the minimum and maximum sum assured
availability.  So the
minimum sum assured available in Niva Rashard 2.0 is Rs 5 lakh.
Maximum is 1 crore.  The
minimum sum assured in HDFCO Optima Secure is Rs 5 crore and the
maximum is Rs 2 crore.  Then comes ICICI Lo
LB where minimum sum assured is Rs 5 and maximum is
unlimited.  This means that if you want
unlimited coverage, then unlimited
sum assured is also available.  The
minimum sum assured in Aditya Bill Active & Max is Rs 5
lakh.  Maximum is Rs 6 crore.  The
minimum sum assured in ManipalCigna Saravaha Param plan
is Rs 5 lakh and the maximum is Rs 3 crore.   Let's
talk about policy tenure.  As you
know, you can take a health insurance policy
for multi-tenure.  So
Neema Reshore 2.0 is available for your one year, two years and
three years.
One year, two year, three year Optima
Super Secure plans are also available in HDFC Ago.  In which
we give three times coverage from day one.
ICICI LBD Elevate has 1 2 3 and recently
they have also introduced four and five years.
Suppose you
want to pay premium for 5 years together.  That
is also a possibility.  What is the benefit to you in
paying premium for 3 years, 4 years, 5 years together?  Firstly, the
company gives you discounts upfront because you are
paying the premium for 3 years, 4 years, 5 years together.
Or secondly, your inflation also gets
protected.  Suppose your
premium may get revised because of inflation.
So if you pay the premium for 3 years
together, then there will be no impact
on your premiums for at least three
years, four years and five years.  So,
you can also choose non-premium.  If
you have any other questions regarding multi-tenure policy like
whether you should take a multi-tenure policy or
not,
we have made a detailed video on that too.  You can refer
if you are considering multi
tenure policy options.
One year, two year and three year options are also available in Aditya Birla Active and Max.
And
in Manipal Cigna Sarvaha Param plan also one year two
year three years option is available.  Now let's talk about
bonuses.  So you
get the bonus in different forms in every policy.
In some cases, no claim bonus is available.  Some
get loyalty addition.  And so on.
So the concept in Nima Booper Reshore 2.0 is
Booster Plus.  Meaning, if you
take a policy of 10 lakhs and you do not use it, then
it will increase up to a maximum of 10 times.
So Booster Plus benefit is available which is
up to 10X.  So basically the
concept here is that whatever sum assured you are
not using will be carried forward
to the next year.  Once you use it, the
remaining balance will be carried forward.
For example, you took a policy of Rs 10 lakh.  If
you use 5 levels, then 5 levels will be
carried forward to the second year.  If
not used, the entire 10% will be
carried forward and the maximum will reach 10
times which is 10X. HDFC Optiemus Secure has a
plus benefit which we just talked about which is a
loyalty addition. Your sum
assured will be enhanced by 50% next year and by another
50% the next year.
By default, you have a guaranteed
cumulative bonus in ICIC LBD Elevate.  Which is 20% of
your sum assured increases every year.  Maximum
increases to 100%.  There is a policy of 10 lakhs.
Next year 12 then 14 then 16 then 18
then 20.  This is also irrespective of the
claim not being reduced.  Your claim is
not based.  This will
not be reduced due to claims.  Even if they take the claim,
your bonus remains intact.
Aditya Birla Active & Max offers
100% of your sum assured increase.  Next
year this is irrespective of claim.
Maximum it goes up to 500%.
Your piggy bank benefit is inbuilt in the Manipal Cigna Saravaha Param plan.
Gullak is basically
100% your sum assured increases.  Maximum
it increases up to 1000%.  This means
your sum assured goes up to 10 times.  If today the
policy is 10 lakhs, next year it is 20, next
year it is 30, 40 and goes up to one lakh a
year.  And this benefit is also irrespective
of the claim.  The claim is not linked.  Day
Care Benefits.  So the day care procedures are
also covered in all your policies.
Up to some assured.  Day care
procedures are those
where, due to the advancement of science, you do
not have a mandatory 24-hour hospitalization.
Those are called day care
procedures.  For example, Cater Act.
You don't need 24-hour hospitalization for that.
You are discharged to day care within the day itself.
So that is also covered.
Up to sum assured in your policies.
Comes Ayush Hospitalization.  Hospitalization is also done for AYUSH,
Ayurveda, Yoga, Unani, Siddha,
Homeopathy.
That too is covered in all your five policies.
Actual domiciliary hospitalization up to some assured S.
Domiciliary
hospitalization is basically
hospitalization at home, meaning if there is a condition where the
patient is critical and cannot be taken to the hospital, then
treatment at home is covered
and or if a bed is not available in the hospital,
then also domiciliary hospitalization will be covered
as per actuals and up to some
amount.
Refill benefit is available in Neeva ReShor 2.0, unlimited number
of times and it stays forever with you.
ReShor Plus is basically available.  So, let
me explain.  Suppose you took a policy of ₹1 lakh
and you took some partial claim of ₹
2 lakh, ₹3 lakh.  So you saved ₹7 lakh.
Now for subsequent claim your
₹1 lakh will be refilled immediately.  And
once refilled, it will always be with you.  If
refilled in Year One, then
in Year Two by default the base sum assured
plus booster balance remaining plus interest
plus.  Meaning the refill is permanently attached to your base.
You should understand this.
So you can enjoy the refill amount in a single claim.
Which is Reader Plus
and This Can Happen Multiple Number of Times.
Your refill is needed again.  The base is
exhausted.  If you need it again, you will get a
refill.  Whatever
your base sum assured is.  If you have 10 lakhs then once 10
lakhs are finished then you will get 10 lakhs again.
And so on.  Now let's talk about
HDFC Ego Optima Secure.  One
time refill is available in it.  Let's say your
base sum assured exhausted.  Now you
need it again in the same year.  So the
insurance company will refill the amount of your base assured so that
you can claim it.  But if you
want to avail this on unlimited refill, you
can do so by paying a nominal
additional premium. This refill benefit is
for any illness, be it related or unrelated illness.
Same in Nivapa as well as HDFC Ergo.
Unlimited number of
times refill is available in ICICI LBA Elevate, equal to base sum
assured for any illness. Same is the case with Aditya Birla
Active One Max.
100% refill is available in this plan and unlimited number
of times if the base sum assured gets exhausted. Same goes
for Manipal Cigna
Sarvah Param plan also for any illness.
Unlimited number of times refill is
available. Emergency road ambulance: So,
when you need a road ambulance at the
time of hospitalization and if you
need an ambulance to go to the hospital, then it
is covered in your policies. But actually there is
no sublimit up to
sum assured.  The cost of emergency
air ambulance will be borne. Many times it happens that the patient cannot be taken
through road or
medical evacuation is required or the place where
you are does not have the facilities or the
condition is critical, then air ambulance
is required.  Nima Reshore 2.0 covers 2.5 lakhs of
air ambulance.  HDFC Ergo
Optima Secure has a cover of 5 lakhs.
You can add on to ICIC LBAD Elevate.
You can get air ambulance cover through add on.
Not covered in Aditya Birla Activ Max.  And Manipal Signal Sarvaha
Param plan also has Edge as an add on.  You
can get it added through add ons.  Annual health
checkup.  So annual health checkup is also a
part of your policy.  So that you
focus on your wellness.  So that illness does not occur.   So that is why
insurance companies focus on providing
you with an annual health checkup once a year.
Like lemon is complimentary in Reshore 2.0.
Annual checkup is
available once a year as per your availability and is done
cashless.
You can get reimbursement from HDFC Ergo Optima Secure.   It is
as per your sum assured.
You can get the health checkup reimbursement as per your requirement once a year
on renewal.  ICICI LBRD Elevate also has
cashless plans on their list.  Aditya Birla
Active One Max also has free list
and cashless treatment on offer.  There is cashless annual
health checkup.  Manipal Sinh Saravaha Param
Plan also offers you a health checkup once a year.
This is inbuilt.  Pre and post
hospitalization expenses.  This means that you can get reimbursed the
expenses before and after going to the hospital.  The
treatment provided should be
related to the reason for which you are being hospitalized.  So pre and
post hospitalization expenses in Neva
Rashord 2.0 is 60 days and 180 days.  HDFC
Ergo Optima Secure also has 60 days and
180 days.  ICIC LBA Daily VAT covers 90
days pre-hospitalization expenses and
180 days post-hospitalization expenses.
You can also get reimbursement of pre-post hospitalization expenses for 90 days and 180 days in Aditya Birla One Activ Max and 90 days and 180 days in Manipal Cigna Sarvaha Param Plan.
Modern Treatments
and Robotic Surgeries
Modern treatments and robotic surgeries are
covered up to some assured in NEEP ReSure 2.0.  There is sublimation on some things in this.
Meaning, your main problems
like heart disease, kidney disease,
cancer, malignancies, organ
transplant, all this is covered up to some
assured.  There are no sublimits on robotic surgeries.
But if you undergo any
elective surgery like knee
replacement, hernia, stone, cataract.
Now if you take their robotic surgeries then you will
get a claim of only Rs 1 lakh.  This is it at the moment
but very soon you will get a rider in this also
so that you can remove this post.  There is
no submission in the remaining four plans.  Your modern treatments,
robotic surgeries are covered up to some extent.
Non-payable items, consumable items.  As
you know, there are some items in health insurance
which are non-payable and
which are mostly not covered in your plans by default.
So for non-payable items,
generally you have to take a rider.
In Nima Boop Reshore 2.0, you
can take Safeguard or Safeguard Plus rider to cover
your non-payable items.  HDFC ago Optima
Secure has an inbuilt Protect Rider
which covers your non-payable items.
You will also need to add a Claim Protector rider to the ICICI LBAD Elevate plan
if you want to
cover non-payable items.
Aditya Bill Active One Max also
covers non-payable items by default.   It
is fully covered.  There is no need to take a separate rider.
Then comes Manipal
Singhana Sarawaha Param.  In this also you have to
enter NME and DME rider.
You will have to add the rider of non-medical expenses and durable medical expenses.
OPD.  So OPD is Out
Patient Department.  There are some expenses
for which you do
not need to be hospitalized.  Suppose you
took a doctor consultation.  You
consulted a doctor, took medicines and came home.  So,
you can get your consultation cost covered through OPD rider.
Acute care rider is covered in Nevapa
where you can get expenses covered up to Rs 20,000.
HDFC Ago has Optima Well
Being Rider which allows you to
consult a General Practitioner,
available both in person and online.  ICIC
LBAD is a B Fit rider in Elvet.
We have made a very detailed video on this also.
So you can refer.  That is the OPD
rider that you can add.  Then comes
Aditya Birla Activ 1 Max OPD
is not available here.
OPD rider is not available in ManipalCigna Sarvaha Param plan
and OPD is not inbuilt either.
Copayment.  So copayment is basically a tool
where you pay some percentage
of the claim and the
insurance company pays the remaining percentage.  Copayment
reduces your premium if you
make a voluntary copayment.  iv But there
is no copayment option in Yash 2.0.  HDFCO
is also not in Optima Secure.  ICIC
LBAD Health Elevate has copayments.
You can choose voluntary copayment.   There
is no copayment in Aditya Birla Activ Max also.  At Manipal Cigna, you
can choose copayment as a rider to reduce
your costs.  Then comes deductible.  Deductible
is Annual Aggregate Deductible.  This means that you agree to pay a
small amount
yourself every year and then
pay the insurance company on top of that.  So this is called annual aggregate
deductible.  The option is available in Neeva Reshore 2.0.
You can add a deductible
to reduce your premiums.
Also available in HDFC Ergo Optima Secure.
ICIC LBAD Health Elevate currently does
not have a deductible available.  But there are
full chances of it coming in the future.  Aditya Bill has
also introduced deductible in Activ Max.
You can take a deductible.  If
you want to reduce the premium.
Deductible option is also available in Manipal Signal Saravaha Param plan.  There
is an optional rider.  You
can choose.  Now let's talk about
waiting periods.  There is a waiting period in Neevapar Reash 2.0.  The
initial waiting period
is 30 days.  The waiting period for this slow-growing illness
is two years.  Which are
specific exclusions.  There are some
lists which are not covered before 2 years.
Which is the standard waiting period
in almost all policies.  Then comes your
pre-existing diseases waiting period.
Here the waiting period will be three years.
But there are some conditions for which
you can reduce the waiting period for pre-existing diseases
to 30 days.  So,
basically you
can reduce the waiting period for BP and diabetes to 30
days.  Now let's talk about HDFC Ergo Optima
Secure.  The initial waiting period is 30
days.  And the waiting period for your specific exclusions is
two years and the
waiting period for pre-existing diseases is
three years.  But now they have introduced A B C
D Ridon.  Where
you have pre-existing diseases like asthma, BP, cholesterol, diabetes
and you
are willing to pay extra premium.  You
can take it on day one i.e. 30 days.  In ICSE Low LBA Elevate also
your initial waiting period is 30 days.   The
waiting period for specific exclusions
is two years and for pre-existing diseases the
waiting period is three years.  Start
riders can choose.  Where you can take care of pre-
existing conditions like asthma, BP,
cholesterol, diabetes on day one.
Which is can be taken on the 30th day.
Waiting period
can reduce it.  Then comes Aditya
Birla Active One Max.  In this also, the
waiting period for your pre-existing disease is
three years.  Specific exclusion is
two years.  The initial waiting period is 30
days.  Now you want to take PD to 30 days.
So here is the chronic care rider that
you can choose.  A B C D and along with it there
are some other things like
if you have undergone angioplasty,
if you have COPD then A B C D Plus
is basically here which you can take for 30 days.  Then
comes Manipal Singhana
Sarawaha ultimate plan.  As if there is no waiting period in this plan.  This is a
zero waiting period plan.  So no
waiting period will be applicable.  But
Thoro investigation will be done before taking the policy.  On
that basis, it will be seen whether you are
medically fit for the policy or not.  Are you
eligible or not?
According to their guidelines, these were the inbuilt
features that we talked about.  Now let's talk about
optional riders.  Which optional riders
are available in your policy?  Let us first talk about
Neevpar e 2.0. The first
optional rider available here is Safeguard that
covers your non-payable items.  Then there is
Safeguard Plus.  A few more extra non-
payable items have been added to what was
in Safeguard.  Next is acute care
which is a rider to OPD and then you have
smart health which includes disease
management.  So disease management covers your BP
and diabetes for 30 days.   Then
comes personal accident.  So
you can also take a personal accidental rider where
accidental death and permanent disability are covered.
Next is hospital cash
benefit.  Where you want to
get daily cash benefit in case of any
hospitalization, you can also choose hospital cash.
Now let's talk about the
optional riders of HDFC Ergo Optima Secure.   The
first optional rider is the Unlimited Restore
Benefit.  Meaning, if you want
your policy to be restored an unlimited number of times,
then you can add unlimited restore benefit.  Then comes
ABCD Rider which
is a newly introduced rider where
your asthma, BP, cholesterol, diabetes are
covered after 30 days.  Then their
rider available is IPA which is
Individual Personal Accident, Accidental
Death and Disability is covered
in this policy.  Then comes the Critical Illness
Rider where
lump sum benefit is paid out for 51 critical illnesses if you
choose that rider.  Next is
Limitless.  Meaning, here if you
choose the limit list and no matter how much
policy you have taken, any claim may come to you.
Suppose you take a policy of Rs 10 lakh and a
claim of Rs 50 lakh comes, then the insurance company will
pay that also.  Next is the Hospital Cash
Benefit where you get daily cash benefit
for every one person who is
hospitalized.  Then there is Optima Well Being.
This is your OPD rider.  The next rider is
parenthood which comes with a waiting period of two years.
Where maternity related
benefits are given to you.  Now let's talk
about the riders of ICIC LBA Elevate.  Here's your durable medical
equipment.  There is a dependent accommodation
benefit.  There are annual health checkups.
Claim protector that covers your non-payable
items.  Annual Health Checkup
Power Booster Here your sum assured
increases by 100% every year.  Maximum there is
no limit.  Power Booster is a unique rider
that has no upper limit.  There
is a policy of Rs 10 lakh.  There is no upside for 20, 30 next year.  Then
comes infinite care.   This
means that whatever your policy is worth and whatever the
claim amount, the insurance company will pay it.
Policy of Rs 10 lakh and claim of Rs 50 lakh came.   The
insurance company will pay the Will Pay even if a claim of Rs 1 crore is received.
If you have
chosen Infinite Care, then domestic air
ambulance cover is an add-on.  Network
Advantage This is basically your add on where
you are a preferred partner network.
If you take treatment there, you will be
given some discount.  But if
you go to other cashless hospitals, you will have to pay a
co-payment.  I have also made a video on this
about tiered network.  So
you can see that in detail if you
want to understand the network advantage more.  Nursing at
home is covered.  Compassionate Visit Inflation
Protector Your sum assured will increase every year at 5% to 6%
based on CPI inflation.  Then comes
Convalescence Benefit
Critical Illness cover which gives you lumpsum benefit
in case any critical illness is
diagnosed.  Personal Accidental Cover Again
Accidental Death and Permanent Disability
is covered.  Jump started what we talked about.
We will bring A B C D conditions on Day One.  Will
bring it in 30 days.  Room
Modifier If you want to upgrade or downgrade your room, you
can get a room modifier.  If you choose co-payment, which is your voluntary
comment, the premium will be
reduced.  Suppose you say
I am ready to pay 10%.
So if you were to pay X premium,
some of X would be reduced.
You will get a discount.  Then comes Beat Be Fit Rider
which is OPD Rider.
Chronic Care Rider is available in Aitya Birla Activ Max.
Brings ABCD plus conditions to Day One.
And you
can also reduce the category of your room.  That
rider is also available.
Riders available in ManipalCigna Saravaha Param Plan
Waiting.  As you know there is no
waiting period in this plan.
Waiting means you can enter a waiting period.
If you do not have any pre-existing conditions,
your premium will be reduced if you choose to wait.  A surplus
benefit where 100% of the sum assured is
paid to you from the first claim.  Meaning two x gets
covered.  Personal accidental cover
options range from Rs 10 lakh to Rs 3 crore.
Accidental death and disability coverage of
non-medical and durable medical
expenses.  This is through the
air ambulance rider to cover your non-medical expenses.
Room Right Modification
You can choose any room or twin sharing basis room.
Voluntary copayment option
is available.  Voluntary deductible option
is available.  So this is a detailed comparison of these five plans.
Now at last you people must be waiting for the
premiums.  I
share the premium with you.  I have calculated that premium
here as an individual premium
and I have
calculated it at the age of 66.  So that gives you an idea of
what the premium is at the age of 66.  But
if you choose any rider, this is
without riders.  Your premium will vary accordingly depending on which optional rider you choose.
So this is the premium on your
screen Reshore 2.0 premium of Rs 10 lakh on Niva
is
65498 HDFCO Optima Secure is 7382
ICIC LBAD Elevate is 53573 Aitya Birla
Activ Max is 5935 Manipal Sna SvaAha Param
is 65354 So these are the premiums and you
can see this and
choose your policy accordingly.  So this premium
that I am sharing with you is the Zone One
premium.  The premium will
depend on the zone where you live.  This was the
detail from my side that I wanted to share with you.  Do
not forget to do your due diligence before buying any policy.
We have brought a summary for you.  But
if you want to understand in more detail then
videos of all these products are available on our channel.
You can also refer to individual videos.
And if you have any questions
you want to ask, reach out to our team
at Buy the Policy.  You can reach out to
them.  You can call on the number given below.  You
can do WhatsApp.  You
can fill out a Google form.  Our team will
connect you.  If you have any questions,
ask in the comment section.  We will
try our best to answer it.  Quick reminder before we go,
if you haven't subscribed to our channel yet, do so.
So that
you never miss such useful information.
If you like the video, please share it
with your friends and family who are
looking after their parents' insurance or are
senior citizens themselves.  If
they find it difficult to get their policy, they will get a lot of help.
See you in the next video.  Till then
stay safe, take care.  Baba bye.